<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Football!</string>
    <string name="fcbString">FC Barcelona</string>
    <string name="rmString">Real Madrid</string>
    <string name="fcbmString">FC Bayern Munich</string>
    <string name="psgString">PSG</string>
    <string name="lpString">Liverpool</string>

    <string name="fcbInf"> Futbol Club Barcelona, also known as Barcelona and familiarly as Barça, is a professional football club,
        based in Barcelona, Catalonia, Spain. Founded in 1899 by a group of Swiss, English and Catalan footballers led by Joan Gamper,
        the club has become a symbol of Catalan culture and Catalanism, hence the motto "Més que un club" (More than a club).
        Unlike many other football clubs, the supporters own and operate Barcelona. It is the second most valuable sports team
        in the world, worth $3.16 billion, and the world\'s second richest football club in terms of revenue, with an annual
        turnover of €560.8 million. The official Barcelona anthem is the "Cant del Barça", written by Jaume Picas and
        Josep Maria Espinàs. Domestically, Barcelona has won 23 La Liga, 27 Copa del Rey, 11 Supercopa de España, 3 Copa
        Eva Duarte and 2 Copa de la Liga trophies, as well as being the record holder for the latter four competitions.
        In international club football, Barcelona has won five UEFA Champions League titles, a record four UEFA Cup Winners\' Cup,
        a shared record five UEFA Super Cup, a record three Inter-Cities Fairs Cup and a record three FIFA Club World Cup trophies.
        Barcelona was ranked first in the IFFHS Club World Ranking for 1997, 2009, 2011, 2012 and 2015 and currently occupies
        the second position on the UEFA club rankings. The club has a long-standing rivalry with Real Madrid.
</string>
    <string name="rmInf">Real Madrid Club de Fútbol, commonly known as Real Madrid, or simply as Real, is a professional football
        club based in Madrid, Spain. Founded in 1902 as Madrid Football Club, the team has traditionally worn a white home kit since
        inception. The word Real is Spanish for Royal and was bestowed to the club by King Alfonso XIII in 1920 together with the
        royal crown in the emblem. The team has played its home matches in the 85,454-capacity Santiago Bernabéu Stadium in downtown
        Madrid since 1947. Unlike most European sporting entities, Real Madrid\'s members (socios) have owned and operated the club
        throughout its history. The club is the most valuable sports team in the world, worth €2.5 billion ($3.4 billion) and the
        world\'s highest-earning football club for 2013–14, with an annual revenue of €549.5 million. The club is one of the most
        widely supported teams in the world. Real Madrid is one of three founding members of the Primera División that have never
        been relegated from the top division, along with Athletic Bilbao and Barcelona. The club holds many long-standing rivalries,
        most notably El Clásico with Barcelona and the El Derbi madrileño with Atlético Madrid. Real Madrid established itself as a
        major force in both Spanish and European football during the 1950s. The club won five consecutive European Cups, and reached
        the final seven times.
</string>
    <string name="fcbmInf">Fußball-Club Bayern München e.V., commonly known as FC Bayern München , FCB, Bayern Munich, or FC Bayern,
        is a German sports club based in Munich, Bavaria, Germany. It is best known for its professional football team, which plays
        in the Bundesliga, the top tier of the German football league system, and is the most successful club in German football history,
        having won a record 25 national titles and 17 national cups. FC Bayern was founded in 1900 by eleven football players led by
        Franz John. Although Bayern won its first national championship in 1932, the club was not selected for the Bundesliga at its
        inception in 1963. The club had its period of greatest success in the middle of the 1970s when, under the captaincy of
        Franz Beckenbauer, it won the European Cup three times in a row (1974–76). Overall, Bayern has reached ten European Cup/UEFA
        Champions League finals, most recently winning their fifth title in 2013 as part of a continental treble. Bayern has also won one
        UEFA Cup, one European Cup Winners\' Cup, one UEFA Super Cup, one FIFA Club World Cup and two Intercontinental Cups, making it one
        of the most successful European clubs internationally.
</string>
    <string name="psgInf">Paris Saint-Germain Football Club, commonly referred to as PSG, is a French professional association football
        club based in Paris, whose first team play in the highest tier of French football, the Ligue 1. The team was formed in 1970 by
        the merger of Paris FC and Stade Saint-Germain. Domestically, PSG have won five Ligue 1 titles, nine Coupe de France, a record
        five Coupe de la Ligue, five Trophée des Champions and the Ligue 2 title once. In international club football, the Parisian side
        have won one UEFA Cup Winners\' Cup and one UEFA Intertoto Cup. PSG is the joint-most successful club in France and one of only
        two French clubs (with Olympique de Marseille) to win a major European club competition. The Parc des Princes has been the home
        stadium of PSG since 1974. The Camp des Loges has served as the club\'s training centre since 1970. The Tournoi de Paris has
        been hosted by the capital club at Le Parc since 1975. PSG shares an intense rivalry with Marseille and contest the most notorious
        football match in France, known as Le Classique. PSG is the second-highest supported football club in France after rivals Marseille.
        Qatar Sports Investments became the club\'s sole shareholder in 2012. The takeover made PSG the richest club in France and amongst
        the richest in the world. The crest and shirt of the club were mainly designed by Daniel Hechter. The traditional shirt is blue with
        a red central vertical bar framed by white edgings.
</string>
    <string name="lpInf">Liverpool Football Club is a Premier League football club based in Liverpool, Merseyside, England. The club
        has won more European and domestic trophies than any other English team with five European Cups, three UEFA Cups, three UEFA
        Super Cups, 18 League titles, seven FA Cups, a record eight League Cups, and 15 FA Community Shields. The club was founded in
        1892 and joined the Football League the following year. The club has played at Anfield since its formation. Liverpool established
        itself as a major force in both English and European football during the 1970s and \'80s when Bill Shankly and Bob Paisley led the
        club to 11 League titles and seven European trophies. Under the management of Rafa Benítez and captained by Steven Gerrard Liverpool
        re-emerged as European champions once again, winning the 2005 UEFA Champions League Final against Milan in spite of being 3–0 down
        at half time. Liverpool was the ninth highest-earning football club in the world for 2013–14, with an annual revenue of €306 million,
        and the world\'s eighth most valuable football club in 2015, valued at $982 million. The club holds many long-standing rivalries, most
        notably the North West Derby against Manchester United and the Merseyside derby with Everton.
</string>
</resources>
